Don't you dare move!
You've the right to remain silent.
Don't you dare move
or else we will shoot you!
Hello, everyone.
How's everyone doing?
Hey Martin, having a Martini, huh?
Hi. How are you?
Good! Good! Good!
Margret, keep serving
sausages to everyone.
- Hey Hites...
- All fine.
- Hello.
- Is she your latest?
Call it the grace of God.
Batook, my friend!
Looking at your success...
makes me really happy.
Human beings should always be happy,
you know.
Because even Gautam's...
'Gambhir' (Serious).
I am the one who's really happy.
Because you didn't come alone...
...for the inauguration
of GJS shipping's new branch.
In fact, you brought
your wife and kids too.
I'll tell you why I
brought them here later.
First call your daughters.
Should I?
Yes.
Ganga!
Jamuna!
Saraswati!
"Ganga...".
"Jamuna..."
" Saraswati!"
So Maalaya, they are my GJS.
My dues cultured jewels.
You've come for the table, right?
Come for the table meaning,
are you com-for-table?
It's a literal translation.
You see, they grew up
in a English surrounding...
...but sometimes their
Indian-ness comes out...
...and the end result is
a totally different translation.
So tell me. Maalaya.
You said call the girls.
Now they are here, so tell me.
Batook... I want my sons Harry,
Harsh and Hulk...
...to marry your three daughters.
I was thinking they can
have a wedding in Turkey...
Maalaya, I am the only
father on this planet...
...who doesn't want his
daughters to get married.
I will never let my
daughters marry anyone... ever!
Call it a curse, or bad luck.
I don't know.
But my family's been enduring
this ill-fate for decades.
Within 3 years of marriage,
my parents split.
My darling wife Hetal...
...passed-away after
delivering my children.
My eldest sister, Hansa.
Her husband divorced her
within 6 months of their marriage.
And my aunt Sarla...
...suffered a hemorrhage after
she returned from her honeymoon.
When things keep occurring often,
it's called a coincidence.
But if it keeps
repeating every time...
...then it's an indication from God.
And a smart man can
understand an indication.
But Batook,
life without marriage and children..
This is the truth, uncle. Believe us.
We're not making kids.
She's saying... we're not kidding.
Oh my. God!
Pops!
Marriage seems to be out of question.
How about a live-in relationship?
What did you say?
I heard that.
You bloody pervert!
My son Hulk meant to say...
Your son isn't hulk he is rascal!
And you... you're not Maalaya
you're a bloody scoundrel.
And you aren't Godhavri
you're a rhino.
Live in relation? Get out! Get out!
Get out!
- Please stop it.
- Get out!
Just go.
And don't take the boat.
Swim all the way back.
'Job down.'
Calm down.
You three are so smart.
You have never thought
about boys till date.
You three are so naive.
Bottom line,
a person should always be straight.
Because... even Taarak Mehta's glasses
are upside down.
Goodnight, papa!
Goodnight... so soon?
My daughters are so cultured.
Jenny, everyone knows
you don't have a boyfriend.
There are lot of girls here,
choose one.
Sherley. Grow up and go up!
What?
Grow up.
I have a boyfriend.
His name is Teddy.
So come on, tell me right now...
...about your boyfriend.
- No way.
If you don't,
I will tell your sisters.
Then listen.
He's a guy who is a little bit crazy.
"When I saw you, I realized sweetheart."
But his tongue slips... day and night.
"Love is crazy, sweetheart."
Jenny. Will you be my wench?
I mean... wife!
Just like Michael Schumacher...
...he wants to be a no.1 car racer.
And just this morning...
he got a golden chance.
The Indian racer has
broken the all time record.
It's a 50 lap race.
And can you believe it, Jennifer?
He's been racing through
the track like a bullet.
Racer no.
3 has now over taken racer. No 2.
And wow! He has now taken
over the lead front the Indian racer.
Wait. What a reply.
Teddy has taken back
the lead with full throttle.
There is no stopping this guy.
Teddy has almost
reached the finish line.
He can see it.
What happened, Roger?
What's wrong with his car'?
I'm out of petrol?
Shit!
...the lead car has come
to a screeching halt.
Just 200 meters away
from the finishing line.
What do I do now?
Yes!
Wow Teddy.
You're so stool?
I mean... you're so cool.
And the winner of today's race,
ladies and gentlemen...
Is Steve Randall.
Hey!
Well done.
Fantastic racing! Fantastic driving!
Sir... sir... sir... I came first
I finished first
Teddy, Teddy this was a car race...
...not a running race.
Okay, here I go.
Love you baby-boo. Yes I do.
I said it once, and I say it too.
I love you.
Oh!
Hey.
I want all the details about you
sweetheart right now
otherwise your sisters.
Look.
Okay...
Alright.
He's the 'apple of my eyes'.
- Huh?
He's the apple of my eyes.
Bunty!
What do you think
when you look at him?
Sometimes I think...
...that he's the son of some rich dad.
I'm here to take you blessings.
You see, I am a huge fan.
I've an audition today.
If I can get your blessings, well...
How about a selfie?
Just one?
But audition? Audition for what?
He's a hardcore rapper.
Still ain't amazed?
Let me pick up the pace.
Grab you. I popcorn... Ready... Go!
You'll see what I mean.
I be putting in the most..
Never meant to brag..
And I never meant to boast..
Other rappers out..
I'ma turn 'em into ghosts..
If you didn't get the..
Memo let me put in the post..
If you didn't get the.
Meme I gotta let you know..
Everytime I wanna spit..
Man I'm never goin' slow..
Everytime I grab the..
Mic I just never let it go..
Like I'm making love..
Baby I just go and I go...
- Extra-ordinary.
- Thank you.
What you just performed
was both extra... and ordinary!
'So what I heard about
the judge was right.'
'He's taken a bribe.'
So my judgment will be.
Before you pass any
further judgment...
...can I perform just one small piece?
Enough of this multiplex...
...now for the single-screen item.
One... two... three... four...
"Your mother-sister...
Mother-sister... Mother-sister..."
May you bones break..
Your head break..
Everyone should rob your dignity..
May you get cursed with bugs,
the bigger the better...
May you get diarrhea.
You're a dogs breed
so bite you own self..
You got messed up..
So you got kicked..
That too so very hard..
"Your mother-sister...
Mother-sister... Mother-sister..."
Impeccable!
But I cleanly understood
every little detail you said...
...about my sister to my mother!
You know Hindi?
I don't know about Bhuvan...
...but you're the one who will
have to pay twice the penalty.
You're disqualified.
I'm flying!
Yeah, you're flying.
Sherley, I am flying - By the way,
you've a boyfriend, right?
How . . How did you know'?
Just took a chance.
Come on... spill, shoot.
Everything about your boyfriend.
- Sherley...
If you tell anyone about this,
I will kick you donkey.
- Meaning?
- I will kick your ass.
His name is Sandy.
But that crazy chap is
always busy with his first love.
And I don't know why...
He gets a kick out of his 'kick'.
"Goal".
Coach... I don't need
to be a substitute anymore.
I am a good player.
Sandy, you're right.
You deserve to be
permanent on the field.
But not as an ordinary player.
As a water-boy!
But coach, he's too good.
- But, he's an Indian.
Indians are only
worthy to be our slaves.
Now get lost...
You... you... Indian.
The coach has lost it.
"You don't deserve to be here..."
"...you Indian."
"You Indian."
Get out of here."
...Indian!"
Now you listen you
while little willies.
Who said that?
That wasn't me.
I didn't say that.
- I said it.
- What...
The aggression from you. I depression!
If you're Sandy, then I am... Sundi!
Sundi?
Sundi!
As long as Sandy's miserable,
Sundi's on cloud nine.
What?
Ba-Ba Black Sheep have you any balls?
Yes, sir... yes, sir... three footballs.
One for the coach... one for his crony...
...and one for the other banana.
Get that idiot!
Sandy, now you die...
I am out of here.
No! No!
- Sandy.
- What happened?
You're suffering from
Split Personality Disorder.
Split...
It's a relatively rare disorder...
Sometimes due to depression...
...or financial problems,
a different personality...
...emerges from inside.
A completely different
person comes out.
And in your case...
- It's DID.
- Dance India Dance?
Dissociative Identity Disorder!
What's that?
Come, let's hang from outside.
- what?
Let's hang out.
Yes.
After studying your case...
...I'll advice you to avoid Indi..
...the I-N-D -I-A-N word.
When you heat this word,
Sundi will take your place.
Because all your life
you've been bullied...
...because of your race and color.
- You mean...
- I am sorry.
Just by hearing this single word...
How is this possible?
- It is possible, Sandy.
How do I explain it to you now?
Sandy.
My head is aching with pain.
Can you ask someone
to get me a black tea?
Sure.
Black!
Sandy!
Just like you change into Sundi
after hearing 'that' word...
...similarly,
when he hears the word 'black'...
Black!
Nurse! Nurse!
- Black!
- White. White.
You called me black...
- I am saying white.
White.
"He's another black..."
Relax.
Will I never get better?
- Of course you will.
Sandy, things do change,
and you will overcome your depression.
And who knows...
someday you'll have enough money...
...to own your own football club.
- Dr. Patel!
Dr. Ganga Patel!
Two minutes. Two minutes.
Remove his black shirt.
Black!
Catch him! Catch him!
Where will I get that kind of money?
You know, my illness,
this buy 1 get 1 free thing...
...it can be cured permanently.
If you help me.
And for that... will you marry me?
Yes!
No!
Why?
We can go in for a live-in
relationship, but... not marriage.
Why?
You want to know?
- Yes, I want to... what!
Then listen.
What? Broken marriages! Death!
- Are you sure?
- Yes, Teddy.
I am 100 percent sure.
- Stella.
- Yes, ma'am.
Stella, will you
please fix this for me?
- But the money...
- Sure ma'am
I mean, honey it's possible that...
what didn't happen...
I mean, what happened with others...
...won't happen with us.
Look here, everyone got married.
Angelina-Brad Pitt.
Nicole.
Shahrukh.
And...
Except for one.
Jenny.
Every man dreams to be wealthy some day.
- what?
I mean... dreams of a wife.
Marries her.
And then...
Ohh...
Two sweet kids like these.
One like a single-screen type,
and other multi-plex type.
Take a look at me once Sarah.
It's just right there.
- Okay, thank you.
You know,
if we have two kids like these...
...do you know what we can say?
One, two, three four...
Our lives' pillars stand
on these two bamboos..
...wigedee wigedee boom boom dhoom dhoom
dhada bhooom pac dhoopac dhoom pac.
Bunty.
Have some cold medicine.
Take a chill-pill.
But, Sarah.
You know that I always come
and visit these special kids.
So you also keep in touch with them.
That's the least we can do.
But marriage... kids?
Just forget it.
Fine... then forget me.
Because now... I will get married to...
...my illness... and death.
- Sandy.
Can I say something Genelia?
I mean Jenny.
I always thought I'll
marry the one I love.
But since marriage
isn't possible, then...
Hold on, Teddy. Wait.
What's the point in stopping me now?
You know, Sarah.
I wanted to start a family with you.
But if not you, then...
Sir... how are the snacks?
Not like my mummy, but okay.
The phone's ringing.
It's a private number.
Papa.
Papa...
what happened?
I have a boyfriend!
What?
This is all that was left to hear.
- Papa...
- Listen to me.
No one ever listens to me.
I have no value in this house anymore.
Papa! Papa! Papa!
Papa! Please try and understand.
The one whom I love, his looks are..
- Quiet!
A person should have brains...
...because,
even Gujarat has a 'Surat' city!
Get that?
This marriage won't last.
It's bad luck. It's a curse.
Even the maids in my house
couldn't escape this curse.
Look at them, all three are widows.
I won't change my decision.
Papa, the maids are gone,
the maids are gone. - Huh'?
- Let bygones be bygones!
- Right.
Papa, we're not going
to be happy without them.
Papa, please let's take this chance.
Papa, let's be positive you know.
This broken marriage and death.
The reason is just so...
The reason's something else...
- Something else?
- Yes.
Tell me... which father in this world...
...wouldn't want his
daughters to get married?
There's a reason.
It's a really big reason.
But I can't tell you.
- Why?
- No. Sorry.
- Sorry...
- But...
- I love you.
- Papa.
Hold on, papa.
This isn't fair.
- I think you should tell us.
I can't believe this.
You have to tell us,
otherwise we will get married.
Yes!
'These girls will
definitely get married.'
'what reason can I give them now?'
'How do I stop this marriage?'
'who will help me?'
"Pasta!"
Batook sir, you're joking.
- Pasta...
You're my oldest customer.
Pizza for you.
We've known each other for years.
Bread for you.
But that doesn't mean
that your Aakhri Pasta...
...will pretend to be your
family astrologer Aakhri Aastha.
Pasta for you.
And you...
I haven't made Lucy
madam's breakfast yet.
How can I be Aakhri Aastha?
Pasta... it's the question
of my daughters' lives.
Don't you want to open many more...
...franchises of Aakhri Pasta
on London Rasta? - Yes.
Just like the McDonalds.
I will help you.
Just go meet my daughters
as Aakhri Aastha.
Mumble some things in Hindi
along with fake astrology predictions...
...and stop these marriages,
that's all.
But just a minute,
I've another idea.
What idea?
Come, come.
The 'mamma-Mia idea.'
- Mamma-Mia?
Get you 3 daughters tubes-tied.
If they can't become mamma
they won't get a husband.
I am joking.
Listen, Pasta!
You must do this job!
And I am not joking!
"Pasta!"
You wanted to know...
...why I wouldn't let
you three get married.
This... is our family astrologer,
Aakhri Aastha.
Truth can be proved wrong.
But not his predictions.
"Pasta!"
The day Batook Patel's
daughter Ganga Patel's husband...
...sets foot in this house, Batook will
immediately suffer a heart-attack.
And he will die.
'Sets foot?'
You're a joking!
"Pasta!"
The day Batook Patel's
daughter Jamuna Patel's husband...
...sees him, Batook will immediately
suffer a heart-attack.
And he will die.
See him?
The day Batook Patel's daughter
Saraswati Patel's husband...
...speaks to him, Batook will
immediately suffer a heart-attack.
Speaks to him?
- No!
- Yes.
Batook Patel's fourth daughter...
- That's enough!
There's no one there.
Understood? Understood!
Aastha sir,
now you only tell us a way...
...where we can find such grooms for
these girls. First word, first step..
Forget it! Forget it!
The question is about
my life and death.
So I'll die.
Papa...
- I'll give up my life for your happiness.
Just a minute.
Patel... Open the third drawer
there's a knife in it.
"Pasta!"
Goodbye!
Papa...
- Stop... - Please.
Let me die.
- what are you doing?
- Leave it.
- What..
Wow!
Finally it's proven that...
...that fathers are
more valuable than love.
Love you.
- You're right, Aastha.
And anyway,
a person should have high values.
Because even Bheem's little.
Chhota Bheem.
Never saw it?
Forget it.
Come, Aastha,
I'll get you some breakfast.
Yummy.
I mean... of course.
What? As soon as I take my first step
towards him, your father will die'?
What?
You mean,
I'll look at him and he'll die?
What?
You mean,
I'll speak to him and he'll die?
Sir...
Hey mister... I don't
have any loose change.
No begging here. Get lost.
Sandy. Wait!
- He's the one whom I love.
- Him?
Yesterday you gave me good news,
and not a bad one, papa.
He takes his first step,
and you get a heart-attack.
The one I love... can never take
a step even if he wanted to.
And today... you. I life, his life...
...both are in my life.
Greetings, papa.
We are lovebirds.
But why do you stare like angry birds'?
We're a couple.
A pair.
Feet.
Sandy.
Tell papa about yourself.
Your hobbies.
Papa... my favorite place...
Paris!
Favorite sport... Para-gliding.
Favorite slippers...
Paragon!
Favorite food... Pear!
Favorite bird... Parrot!
When I get fever...
I take Paracetamol.
I always watch... Paramount films.
I never talk in sentences...
only in paragraphs.
There's "feet" in every line,
but his feet only don't work.
- What?
- Papa.
I mean... what else is going on, son?
What's going on?
Everything else is going,
except for me...
...who isn't going anywhere.
How will he do?
Papa, your heart will keep
beating if he doesn't walk...
...so he will have to do.
Did you have to settle for him?
Teddy!
Teddy, stop.
Papa... Gracy, this is the man I love.
Your son-in-law will see you,
and you will get a heart-attack.
Look at him, poor guy can't see.
Go on, Teddy. Meet papa.
Papa... love is blind.
But in my case,
the lover is blind, papa.
Teddy, to you right.
- Papa's over there, please go there.
Yes, that's papa.
Papa, how are you?
Papa, I had a feeling...
...you will condom me.
- Huh!
I mean... condemn me.
Teddy, tell him about yourself.
Your likes, your dislikes.
- Yeah.
Myself Teddy.
My favorite color...
Black.
My friends call me 'Justice'.
Because Justice is blind, papa.
When I play cards,
I always play blind.
I was born in the ICU.
And my bank I use is ICICI.
I swear on my mother... papa.
Hold on.
Where did you find him?
- Papa, we met on a blind date.
Open your eyes, dear.
Can't you see that he can't see?
But papa, he's the reason I can now see
you for the rest of my life. - - Who's he'?
In all this show-and-tell you
didn't see what you should've seen.
And what you saw isn't worth seeing.
Open your eyes and see for yourself.
Who's that?
Who's coming now?
He's here.
Look, he's here.
Meet my love. Bunty.
Oh, Sarah.
Papa, you were saying you son-in-law
will speak... - I get it.
The one you said I love you,
can't say it back.
Okay.
Love is cute.
But...
In this case, the lover... is mute.
Tell us something about yourself.
Okay.
My favorite song...
"speak... speak ...speak... Mr. Bachchan."
"Listen. What say Mr. Bachchan?"
- Hey... is there dance show going on'?
AB.
CD.
I am a CD player that's...
Singham?
Itchiness?
...whose speaker... is blown.
My sweety ...my love...
wow! Superb! Great.
All lines in this mute are amazing.
No I-phone.
No talk-time.
No balance.
- Papa...
- Come on, don't worry.
Papa, think of the coincidence...
we sisters
hit the eye of a bull.
We hit the bulls-eye.
Let's take a selfie.
Come on, Teddy.
We'll all stay together now until
we get married. - Wait, wait.
"Sometime she Minks,
sometimes she winks."
"But all the time
links my eyes with hers."
"Sometime he blinks,
sometimes he winks."
"But all the time
links my eyes with his."
"The moons showing attitude."
"Even the sun's talking gibberish."
"In this awesome weather
give me a English kiss."
"Bloody love..."
"Bloody love... From today
love will be like a prayer."
"Bloody love..."
"Bloody love... From today
love will be like a prayer."
"Bloody love..."
"Bloody love... From today
love will be like a prayer."
"Bloody love..."
"I've a desire to die again."
"Because of the way
my tormentor killed me."
"You came walking on a velvet carpet."
"Then how did your feet get hurt?"
"You pierced my heart with you eyes."
"My heart's totally
blossomed by love."
"Bloody love... From today
love will be like a prayer."
"Bloody love..."
"Bloody love... From today
love will be like a prayer."
"Bloody love..."
"Bloody love... From today
love will be like a prayer."
"Bloody love..."
I'll have to test these three rats.
"If you become my dear, like
a small baby I'll take care of you."
"when we're in love, then
why did your father call the priest?"
"I've just one thing to say to you,
I sweat..."
"...you're stuck to
me like chewing gum."
"Oh baby, have mercy on our love."
"You're my bread, and I am your jam."
"Ba Ba Ba Ba Black sheep,
have you any wool?"
"My heart's lost in your lanes."
"Also Jack and Jill went up the hill."
"Come on baby to the
garden of love and chill."
"You're my life..."
"My heart beats for you, baby."
"Now come make me your lady."
"You're my life..."
"Just keep the fun flowing."
"No stopping and no slowing."
"The moons showing attitude."
"Even the sun's talking gibberish."
"In this awesome weather
give me a English kiss."
"Bloody love..."
"Bloody love... From today
love will be like a prayer."
"Bloody love..."
"Bloody love... From today
love will be like a prayer."
"Bloody love..."
"Bloody love... From today
love will be like a prayer."
"Bloody love..."
"Bloody love... From today
love will be like a prayer."
what are you thinking, Teddy?
Come on, jump.
Don't worry.
Can you see the water?
I mean heat the water.
It's filled with water. It's full.
It's full.
Look... warm water. Warm water.
Look.
Come on. I am right here.
Just jump, and we'll swim together.
- Teddy.
- What?
Jump.
- No. Papa. I can't jump today.
Why?
I am observing a fast today...
no-water fast.
I don't drink on this day,
and definitely not bathe.
Just jump,
papa's doing the countdown.
One...
Two...
Three...
To hell with the money.
Papa!
He's definitely a 100 percent blind!
Maria!
Get the vacuum!
Suck the ants from my pants!
Oh my, God!
Bitten!
- He 200 percent can't walk.
For sure papa's going
to test you as well.
He really can't walk,
that's why he passed the test.
Now you don't utter
a single word.
Not a single word should
come out of your mouth, get it?
"Pasta!"
Hello!
He cut me, threw me
and he shoved up my...!
Mommy!
"Bloody love..."
Teddy, what are you doing here?
Don't worry.
In this house, I am blind.
And I've convinced your papa as well.
And you convinced me as well...
...that there's no
such thing as astrology.
Nothing happened to papa.
Of course.
It's fixed for every person, you know.
- what?
Package.
Age... I mean papa's age.
Kids of a gun'?
- What?
- Son of a gun!
By the way, how's this top?
Teddy?
My sisters and my best friend Shirley
is getting married tomorrow.
We all have to go together.
That's fine my Jenifer Lopez.
But before that... how
about we rehearse for our wedding?
Teddy. Stop it!
"I'm gonna start the ignition..."
"...of you inner emotions."
"For manual operation
with mutual consideration
for production of
future generation."
Shh.. Sandy, Teddy might heat you.
We're all in one house.
You keep spoiling my mood.
Hey ...what happened?
What happened?
I don't understand how
those two weirdos got in this house?
Duh! Hello... they both were
already in this Housefull.
You entered later.
So you better watch out for them.
But meanwhile, just keep watching me.
Understand?
Darling, under is fine,
but don't say stand.
Since I came in this house,
I've been only sitting.
It's been ages since I last stood up.
But tonight...
let's stone and roll, Sandy.
Stone, roll?
Let's rock and roll.
- Not on the lips?
- Not yet.
After we're married.
Wow, Sandy.
You proved today
that you really love me.
And you know the
best part about you is?
Even though you live here, those Indian
values and culture still exist in you.
My phone, hold on a second.
"I'll have to airlift
the Indians living in Kuwait."
"The Indians living in Kuwait... Indian."
He needs so much attention.
"London Bridge is falling down...
falling down... falling down."
"Come, let's get this party started,
party started, party started."
I'll call you back.
- Sandy?
- Not Sandy... Sundi.
And now you're going to be helpless...
...cause I am going to lock the door.
Jack... Lean on me!
- No, Sundi.
- Sandy! Sandy!
Yes, Sandy. Wait.
- No, Sundi.
- Sandy!
Sandy.
No.
- Soap!
- Oh my, God.
Where's a towel?
Help me.
Idea.
Sandy, fall asleep,
Sundi will sleep too.
- Good idea, good idea.
- Sleep.
'Rock-a-by baby..."
"Come to me my lady."
"bowl of milk!"
- Help me!
Am I a doctor?
I am the one having bad luck.
One can't speak, one can't
see and the other one can't walk.
Good morning, Papa.
What's so good about it?
Come on, Batook. Let's exercise.
Good morning, Sandy!
- Good morning!
- Hey...
- what?
What?
Just now you were playing,
and now you're sitting.
This is leg-lines for papa,
and not headlines.
- Now you'll be feroze.
- Feroze.
I mean exposed.
Now the wealth will be
divided in only two parts.
What will tell papa?
That you're a liar.
You were playing football.
I saw it with my own eyes.
Yes, go tell him.
Go tell him that a blind
man was seeing with his eyes.
Go on.
Yes... I will tell him,
that I saw with my own...
- Yes, go tell him.
- Shit.
You bloody rascal...
Got the rhythm down pat..
Get ready!
About to hit the stage you raise..
Desi bad boi sharpin
in the razor blade..
Is the CD player on?
Got swag on lock..
Let em haters hate...
Got em thinking like man he great..
Down pat..
Get ready!
About to hit the stage you raise..
Desi bad boi sharpin
in the razor blade..
Got swag on lock..
Let em haters hate...
- Got em thinking like man he great..
You were right.
Make em say..
Right now just shake, shake..
Now the wealth will be divided in only two
parts. - Right now just shake, shake..
Come on, shoot that.
- Right now just shake, shake..
Kill em.
Who be the best on the mic..
Better tell em..
Right now just shake!
Kill em.
That... was total crap.
What?
"Your mother-sister...
Mother-sister... Mother-sister..."
Done?
Now, listen to your favorite song.
"Speak... speak... speak... Mr.Bachchan."
"Listen. What say Mr. Bachchan?"
"speak... speak... speak... Mr.Bachchan."
"we shot everything Bachchan."
Now... you're unmasked.
I mean papa... will come...
- And first watch...
...your single-screen
performance on this multiplex thing.
Speak... speak... speak... Mr.Bachchan."
"Listen. What say Mr. Bachchan?"
what do you two think?
Only you two can shoot a video?
Maria, have you seen my phone?
I'm supposed to get an important call.
Has anyone seen my phone?
Have you seen my stick, papa?
Get lost. I am supposed
to get an important call.
For our own good, we must
divide the wealth in three shares.
And instead of ruining each other...
...we should look out for each other.
Who says money divides?
The girls' money...
is going to make us rich.
"Expensive liners,
and those dangly earrings."
"The glittering skirt..."
"...and the way you sway
that waist is priceless."
"Expensive liners,
and those dangly earrings."
"The glittering skirt..."
"...and the way you sway
that waist is priceless."
"You make me skip a beat, sweetheart."
"In this world..."
"You're the richest girl in London,
sweetheart."
"You're the richest girl in UK,
"You're the richest girl in the world,
sweetheart."
"Handsome, dashing, smart
boys... they all want to be my man."
"You're the one who stole
the peace of my heart."
"when I walk, when I talk,
when I watch my sweetheart."
"There's no one else,
as gorgeous like you."
"I've said yes,
now take me along darling."
"In this London..."
"You're the richest guy in London,
darling."
"You're the richest guy in UK,
"You're the richest guy in the world,
darling."
"Your fair cheeks,
you black tresses."
"You look so sexy."
"Your gorgeous body..."
"Your gorgeous body, blows my mind."
"Your hot figure, blows my mind."
" Anyone you trap,
only God can save him."
"I've never seen anyone like you."
"Life is short,
let's say those sweet-nothings."
"If you say it once,
I'll do anything for you."
"This is your chance,
and also the ritual..."
"...but why you standing far."
"Take me in your arms,
like a true prince."
"Hello to everyone from me,
sweetheart."
"In this world..."
"You're the richest girl in London,
darling."
"You're the richest girl in UK,
"You're the richest
girl in the world, darling."
"You're the richest, girl."
"You're the richest, darling."
Yes.
Yes... don't worry.
Your daughters Ganga, Jamuna,
Saraswati are absolutely fine.
Yes, yes the wedding
date has been fixed.
Okay.
Ganga, Jamuna, Saraswati are
not your daughters? - No.
And if you want to open
more franchises in London...
...then you must keep this a secret.
Okay... my lips are sealed.
But then who is their father?
Urja Nagre.
You mean that... that...
- Yes, him.
Once upon a time
Mumbai's most fierce Don.
- And I was his right-hand.
- You?
Since the he used
to rule the city of Mumbai.
What's this Shinde'? You planned
my assassination?
Ruling the city of Mumbai...
and annihilating his enemies...
...was BHK for him.
- BHK'?
- By left hand's play.
His principles were stronger
than his enemies' intentions.
Urja trafficking minor
girls is a very profitable business.
What do you say?
He was the Godfather...
...but an even better father
to his three daughters.
Due to the pressure built
up by raids and secret operations,
...by Maharashtra Police's the
Underworld has come to a stand-still.
Even big and powerful personalities...
...are either getting
arrested or fleeing.
'But just then... one of Urja
Nagre's enemies informed the police.
Come on!
Let my children go!
Let my daughters go!
Hey!
No! No!
Patel... Leave Mumbai and go to London.
I've got some property out there.
You've a clean record.
You'll be the caretaker
of my children.
You give them your name.
Raise them and get them married.
And give my wealth
to them and their husbands.
Did you get the bank papers?
But Patel... my daughters...
...should never know that
I am their real father.
Mother of the brownie cookies.
He's Ram... and you're Lakhan.
- Yes.
- Papa-pia.
You took on the responsibility
of such a big man.
Wowwie.
But a thousand curses to the informer...
...that got Urja caught.
He's a dog, he's a rascal... - Stop it.
How much are you going to abuse him'?
You act like I am abusing you.
You're right.
I got Urja Nagre caught.
But you were his 'woof...
his loyal aide.
A man should be a traitor...
Even dogs are loyal.
All my life I've been lying.
I told my daughters that
marriages don't last in our family.
Lie.
Those predictions... also a lie.
The truth is... I always had
my eyes on Urja Nagre's wealth.
And that's why I want his three girls...
...to marry my three sons,
and not someone else.
You own sons? Who?
Same guys who were released
from jail yesterday.
My boys.
No one has the guts...
to stop us now.
to stop us now... until the wedding.
Wait a minute. Wait a minute.
INDIAN.
I don't believe it.
This one word... India...
- Don't say it.
- Quiet.
- Sorry.
I mean... when you hear this one word,
you turn into Sundi'?
Is this a lifetime illness?
- Only four days!
Four days later,
after we're married...
...I will be cured.
I'll have money... no depression.
Set.
I've a huge treasure-chest
waiting for you...
...but you three are busy
stealing pennies and dimes.
Dad... a tailor's son...
...is going to stitch
clothes for a living.
Crime runs in our blood.
True.
The main agenda is to stop
...those blind, mute and crippled
guys from marrying the girls.
The easiest way out of this problem...
...is that we take those
three someplace and shoot them.
Wonderful. Shoot! Murder!
A dog's tail will always stay crooked.
Try to understand
the important point here.
If your lentils gets spoiled,
your day is spoiled.
If your pickle gets spoiled,
the whole year is spoiled.
- What?
- What what?
Shut up.
The main point here is
that your father's still here.
I will find a way out of this.
Dad, you don't dig
a well when there's a fire.
Try to understand our point.
You've made a very simple plan.
But it's a sure-shot plan.
A person should be simple.
Because... even VIP
is an underwear brand.
Did you get a word what he said?
- Nah!
Whatever.
Bunty, you know Batook's dog...
I mean his daughter.
- what crap do you keep saying?
You know I've so many dreams
to fulfill once I marry her.
I see... tell me.
Once I get the money,
I'll sponsor a car for myself...
...and become Grand
Prix's top Indian racer.
Indian.
Even I'll use my money
to make a music album...
...and it will be the best
Indian album in the world.
My songs will be played
in the Indian Premier League.
India Pro-Kabaddi League.
Now it will be an Indian wedding.
What the!
Sundi is back!
I am going to Batook Patel.
To expose you, you... and Sandy.
Stop me if you can.
I will expose you all!
We must stop him.
- Come on.
I am coming, Batook!
Pakistani.
- Pakistani.
- What are you doing?
If Sundi can come out hearing Indian...
...then maybe he can go back
hearing Pakistani. - Yes.
- Pakistani.
- Iraqi.
- Afghani.
- Kuwaiti.
- Dubai.
- Nepali.
No country can stop Sundi today.
Not countries, But now
these two states will stop Sundi.
- UP...
- And Maharashtra.
Hey!
Catch him!
Spin!
He's fallen. Bunty, catch him.
Not me, catch him.
You sure did eat a lot.
Why you..
- Sorry, sorry, sorry.
- Why you!
- You dog...
- Sorry, sorry...
Now there's just one way to stop him.
Break his legs for real.
Careful!
You guys can't hurt Sundi.
Sundi will hurt himself.
Batook, where are you?
Let's go, quickly.
Batook, look at my legs.
Papa, he's sitting down only.
Hickory, Dickory... and Dock.
I can walk...
...and this rascal... can talk.
Cheating.
Yes, cheating.
These cheaters have
played hide and skirt..
I mean hide and seek papa.
I am blind,
but couldn't you see it papa?
- Come blind one.
What?
You think if I catch the
ball you'll prove I am not blind?
I am blind.
I am blind, papa.
Take that!
What?
You think if I catch the brick
you'll prove I am not blind.
I am blind.
I am blind, papa.
I am not blind.
- He caught it.
- Yes.
I am not blind.
Open your eyes and
take a look, Batook.
We're exposed.
Throw us out of the house.
You can even slap us with these hands...
Sandy, what did you Sundi do?
OMG... what the?
You guys ruined papa's wax statue.
Gosh!
Good Lord.
How are you going to fix this, Jenny?
What happened?
Congratulations, guys.
It was a wax statue.
And we thought... it was dad.
But seriously guys,
are you guys walnuts?
- Walnuts?
- Are you guys nuts?
Oh...
The whole hand is disfigured.
We want to gift this to
papa next week on his birthday.
- Sorry. Really sorry.
- Sorry.
Oh yes, why don't we
go fix your broken wheelchair.
Yes. Let's go fix that
before her father returns.
Come, Bubbly... I mean, Bunty.
We'll be right back.
Fix your father's hand,
and we'll be right back.
They don't understand.
- Hurry up.
It's not about the wax...
...it's about our feelings for papa.
You're right Jenny.
Whatever we are today,
it's only because of our dad.
Yes, Shafiq, I saw your missed call.
I was driving.
I went to pee, and you sat down.
I was only checking
whether it's working or not.
No need to get angry.
It's so cute, isn't it?...
I see... so you were eyeing those two.
- Yeah, it's amazing.
Ogling at girls from
behind the glasses.
So what are you doing tonight?
I don't know,
I was thinking to maybe go out.
Not sure, what about you?
Hey baby, let's go for a ride.
- Oh my, God. Get off me.
Take it easy, guys.
Now like this gun,
you guys will RIP.
Rest... In... Pieces!
Isn't... that Urja Nagre?
Mumbai's Don?
But wasn't he in jail?
Don't ever think of doing
this... in your wildest dreams.
Hold it guys, hold it.
Please hold it.
I would appreciate if you
guys had taken a slight effort...
...to stop these goons.
We should use our hands for a cause,
not just applause.
Please leave, guys. Please.
Come on, come on.
Come on, let's leave.
And you three.
You guys look like your from India.
Thank God he didn't say Indian.
What did you say?
You three should be ashamed.
Those goons were
harassing those girls...
...and you three were simply watching.
But we poor guys are disabled.
- I...
- You're crippled.
He's mute.
And... I am blind.
Get something to eat.
We'll split this in dues ways.
- Give it to me.
Hey... what's going on'?
- Flies.
- Flies are bothering us.
What's Nagre doing in London?
If he's in London, that means
someone's surely going to die.
"Take some rice, and some
lentil and top it off with curd."
"One who harbors no enmity,
is the happiest person on this earth..."
A... T... M!
Any Time Money?
Today I'm going to beat you.
Urja. You're in London?
When did you come out from jail,
Urja?
Seeing my good behavior,
the government...
...pardoned the rest of my sentence.
After getting released from jail...
...I thought of coming
here and surprising you.
And to see my daughters once.
Not like a father, but as a stranger.
But just see them.
But Shafiq called
before I could call you.
That arms dealer from London.
He informed me... that you're
getting my daughters married...
...to some guys who are not normal.
What?
What did I say?
My daughters should never
know what tears ate.
Didn't I say that?
Is that all you know?
- what do you mean?
What do you mean?
I had chosen dues
capable and normal boys.
That's why I called you
to say there's a wedding at home.
But then I found out that...
...the boys you. I daughters
love are not normal.
I tried explaining the girls.
I said "Please don't marry Teddy,
Bunty and Sandy".
But for you daughters,
love is blind, love is mute...
...and love is crippled!
This is how I'm
rewarded for my loyalty?
Sorry, Patel. Sorry.
I am a father after all.
But Patel, I must see what's
right and what's not for my daughters.
Tell me... where will I find
those normal boys for my daughters?
You will... I'll show you.
He's an expert in
transporting people upstairs.
He... satisfies his hunger
by feeding others.
And he... cleans 250,000 shoes every day.
These are the three boys.
And Urja, I forgot
to tell you one important detail.
All three boys are orphans.
No, Patel, they are not orphans.
They are like Kohinoor diamonds.
What diamonds?
Human beings should
be like human beings.
Even a rice brand is called Kohinoor.
Patel, my daughters
will marry these three boys only.
When are those three
boys getting married?
Saturday.
You mean... WTF.
What the...
Wednesday... Thursday... Friday!
We have three days
to stop their marriage.
This looks stunning.
- Look at it, Gracy.
It's really beautiful.
Isn't it?
Oh, look at that,
that's really pretty.
"You're the richest
of all sweetheart."
Girls, why do we love these losers?
"You're the richest
of all sweetheart."
Because...
- we're so crazy about them.
- Yeah.
"And I found love... when I found you."
"Because I need you...
when I say I love you."
"And I found love..."
"Oh baby, please stay."
"I need you... when I say I love you."
Hello. Enough decoration for the day.
It all looks beautiful.
Batook sir, you're going
to wear this for the wedding.
Yes, Maria, it's fine.
I won't let this wedding happen!
Who is he?
Urja! The don has come.
Don! Don! Don! Hide.
- Dead for sure.
- Who? Papa?
- No, us.
- Why?
I am mute for your papa,
but for Urja Nagre I am crippled!
I am crippled for your papa,
but for Urja Nagre I am blind.
I am blind for your papa,
but for Urja Nagre I am nude.
You're mute, how can you be nude?
Then you three should stay away
from the lemon's light. - Yeah.
Lemon's light?
What does you girl keep saying?
She's saying limelight.
Nimbu means lime, Roshni means light.
What else?
But how?
Idea. Cover your
faces the bead strings.
Urja, Urja... what are you doing here?
Before I went to jail,
I had loaned you some money.
You thought I'll
never get out of jail?
Here you're busy preparing
for you daughters weddings.
For the world you are good
but for me you're a traitor.
Pay up... or I won'!
Let this wedding happen.
- Mister.
- What?
How much does he owe?
One million, five million...
10 million... 50 million?
Papa will pay it back.
With interest,
he owes me 50 billion.
Oh my. God!
Papa, that kind of money
one borrows for the entire country...
...and not for yourself.
Quiet!
Urja I'll be out on the streets.
And we'll be flat-bloke.
I'm begging you,
don't tarnish my honor.
Forgive me.
- You guys beg him too.
- Yes...
Come quickly.
Help me.
Come on, quickly.
Yes.
Everyone take their turban off.
- Urja.
- Say sorry.
Sorry...
Urja, take pity on these mute,
crippled and blind guys.
He'll see our faces.
- Hide your faces.
Look at their innocent faces.
Show him your faces.
Show it! Show it!
It's hand to make out who's blind,
mute or crippled.
Aren't you the same
guys I gave money to?
I'll forgive you on one condition.
What condition?
Marriage.
You want to marry Batook?
Not me... my dues sons have
been waiting to get married
to Batook's daughters.
Let me call my sons.
My three tigers.
Rohan. Rishi. Rajeev.
Look straight blind one.
Papa...
- Yes. - Yes.
I was talking to Batook.
Say yes.
If we get married,
what about you heart attack?
What about your predictions?
I owe him 50 billion.
I'll have no future if I don't pay up,
so what will I do with the predictions?
Dad...
- Yes... - Yes.
I was talking to Urja sir.
- Say yes.
- Yes.
Can we adorn the rings right here?
Yes, with you blessings,
we can do it now?
Mister... can we get some
time to repay the loan?
Fine.
- 10...
- Months.
That's a lot of time.
- 9... 8... 7... 6...
- Cheating.
5...
Sir...
Sir... at least give them
10 days to repay the loan.
Please say yes, sir.
- Please say yes, sir!
- Fine.
I'll give them a chance
to repay the loan.
But now... we'll stay with them.
Patel... for the next ten days,
you house is full.
Bloody dog.
Watch where you fall.
Hello Urja.
Patel, I've been
washed out before in life.
Betrayed?
- I mean apples, grapes...
I've washed them before I ate them.
They're all clean, right?
- Yes, of course.
A person should always be clean...
...even the movie is
named Dirty Picture.
Vidya Balan's... you didn't see it.?
Patel, I was thinking...
This '50 billion plan'
benefited you the most. Right?
Years later you finally
got your chance.
Patel, a drop can't quench
the thirst of the ocean.
How can I quench this
18 year old thirst in 10 days'?
Batook, I hope these days go ASAP.
- As soon as possible?
As slow as possible. Slowly.
But Patel, whatever I went through
is because of that one man.
The one who got me arrested.
The day I find out
who that traitor is...
...he will DIE by my hands.
- Full form?
- No full form.
He will die!
Come Urja.
You said you want to
keep an eye on them 24/7.
So I called everyone.
We'll have dinner together.
Start.
Thanks.
Margret, get the rice.
Let me get that for you.
- You're blind too, remember.
What happened?
Nothing, it was hurting.
Teddy.
If you don't mind me asking...
No offense, but... how did
this incident happen to you'?
' I'm blind and mute.
What do I say now?'
Once on the clock...
No! Guys, guys...
I mean once upon a time.
Teddy was giving his practical
exams at the chemistry lab.
And by mistake...
some acid fell in his eyes.
It pained so much...
...that he cried really loud all day.
'I see... acid in his eyes...
that's why he went blind.'
'I see... he lost his voice
because he cried out loud so much.'
And what happened with you, Sandy?
Behind the long clock...
Guys... long time back.
He met with an accident...
...while clicking a
photo on a terrace.
'Went blind taking pictures?"
'Became crippled taking pictures?"
Because... the poor guy was holding
the camera backwards.
The camera flashed in his eyes...
...and he fell down from the terrace.
'I see...'
'He went blind because of the flash.'
'He became crippled due
to falling from the terrace.'
You guys told us about these two.
But what is Bunty's story?
Why don't you tell us, mister?
Or will someone else tell us?
'She will save me.'
The clock stopped.
Hey guys... time stopped.
When I got the news that some goon...
Some goon shot him with a knife.
I picked him up in a hospital...
and took him to the ambulance.
This crazy girl is
going to get me killed.'
But there... his father got his mother.
But his mother didn't get his father.
What nonsense are you saying?
Don't hide it.
Don't hide anything from them.
If you can't say it, then let me.
I'll tell them.
This happened when he was still...
in his mother's womb.
Like a Cowboy's lasso,
the umbilical chord...
...wrapped around his neck first,
and then his legs.
And you all know what
happened with him next?
What makes me sad is that...
...you called us handicapped
guys at the dining table...
...and want to heat stories
about how we became handicapped!
If you want to hear stories,
then I'll tell you one.
I had a friend, Ashok Fitnis.
Poor guy didn't have both arms,
both legs, one eye...
...and he had just one hobby.
To travel.
His family once took
him to Mahabaleshwar...
...in a plastic bag.
While showing him the valleys,
the bag tore...
...and he fell in the valley.
And he was no more.
I'll tell you all more stories.
- Enough! Enough!
What kind of stories is he telling?
- Enough.
They are getting very emotional.
How much salt are you going
to throw on our wounds - Please.
You've emptied the entire shaker already?
- Come.. Let's go girls.
Please... let's give them some space.
- Listen... listen to my story.
Listen!
We're in deep trouble.
We've only 10 days...
- 9!
Now we must pay
50 billion in 9 days.
And on top of this, that Rohan...
He was touching my sister-in-law
in all the wrong places.
I am very panty about her.
- what?
I mean senti about her.
Shut up you two.
What can two cripples, two blind
and two mute guys do in this house?
Shit.
There's a lot we can do.
I have a plan.
Who's out there?
Urja, you're still awake.
Both of them are coming.
Who's blind, who's mute?...
I...
Give me the cane.
He's crippled not me.
What's up?
What are you guys doing?
It's 'Janmastami'
(Indian Festival) in India.
And this is the only
way we can celebrate it.
"Gopala below."
"Gopala in the middle."
"And Gopala on the top."
'There's a commotion all over town."
"Here comes Krishna of Brij..."
"...take care of your pots."
" Govinda!"
Guys... guys...
Guys...
Guys, please.
Please... guys.
Listen...
what's the plan?
Guys. Guys.
Guys, listen to me!
We've come up with a plan.
It will clean the debt...
...and get those there villain
out of our lives.
Jenny, tomorrow is the St.
Patrick's Beer Festival at wembley.
We'll call Urja's boys
there and get them drunk.
And as soon as we get out chance,
we'll reward them.
Meaning?
Meaning Rajeev, Rohan and Rishi...
You all have got to sleep with them.
What?
I mean seduce them.
- Listen to me.
- No way.
It's really simple...
why did you slap me?
You're always hitting me.
Listen to me!
"We're going to dance all night..."
"we're going to dance all night..."
"...with our feet in the air."
"Everyone drunk today..."
"Switch off the lights... tom,
dick and harry."
"Steal this moment,
don't think you silly."
"Every part of your
body's going to rock..."
"...with our feet in the air."
"we're going to dance all night..."
"I am a bottle of wine..."
"...that's completely intoxicating."
"All the guys want a piece of me."
"I am cutie-cutie..."
"And a little naughty."
"You and me have a great chemistry."
"You're divine baby."
"Always hitting on me, baby."
"I feel so fine, fine, fine."
"Let's dance like Govinda..."
"...with our feet in the air."
"Everyone drunk today..."
"Don't stop me."
"I want to dance."
"Put up your hand,
the music's playing loud."
"I am going to dance all night."
"Don't stop me."
"I want to dance."
"Put up your hand,
the music's playing loud."
"I am going to dance all night."
"The place is houseful..."
"...DJ raise the sound."
"Sway that waist all you like."
"Let's shake that waist..."
"...with our feet in the air."
"Switch off the lights... tom,
dick and harry."
"Steal this moment,
don't think you silly."
"Every part of your
body's going to rock..."
"...with our feet in the air."
"we're going to dance all night..."
would you guys like
something to drink? No?
Margret, get me some kokum juice.
We found some good boys.
- Didn't I tell you so?
Guys, next monsoon...
...your sister-in-law will be mom soon.
What? You too?
You mean, last night...
- with Gracy.
Even I do the right
things in the dark.
Cheers.
- Do you know how?
- How?
Like this!
Blindfold?
Handcuff?
Whip?
But how do you know?
Because last night you three...
...slept with these three.
After you got drunk.
And this calls for... Papa! Urja!
Ganga! Jamuna! Saraswati!
Papa... sir...
Last night your three
sons slept with the housemaids.
No, no, we... we... didn't want
to sleep with them.
Right!
They wanted to sleep with us.
And that too before the wedding papa!
So these are the guys
you were advocating for.
Batook sir, now we want justice!
Compensation or rape charges!
Yes!
My advice is that you su-su on them.
I mean... sue them twice.
Once for rape,
and once for compensation.
Sue-sue!
Urja... take my advice... and
give them 5000... - Billion.
50 billion!
Have you lost it?
First ask for your 50 billion.
- Oh yes.
First give me my 50 billion.
Let's sit down and make a deal.
No need to point...
'He's mute, how can he...'
I did.
Should I say it again?
Let's sit down and make a deal;
No need to point.
Mimicry artist.
'Oh, Sandy said it.'
'Hold on... Sandy's blind.'
'How did he see his finger?'
There were two of them.
One spoke and the other saw.
Come back to the 50 billion.
How did the mute guy speak?
I did. I did.
I said come back to
the topic of 50 billion.
It's really simple, Urja.
- Did you see?
I am blind.
Do I have to explain?
Now listen carefully, Urja.
You have to take 50 billion from him.
Right?
And you've to compensate
50 billion to the girls...
...because of your sons
misadventures last night.
So papa will transfer
it in the maids' accounts.
So considered that settled.
He'll pay them.
End of the matter, right?
- Papa... sir...
- who said that?
All we know is we don't
love your sons, we love them.
Enough!
Now there's going to be two weddings.
First, my sons will marry the maids.
Yes!
And Batook's daughters
will marry these poor chaps.
- Yes!
- Put me down, put me down!
Sarah, now tell us
why you brought us here?
I know, the girls
are getting desperate.
Even two days are too much for them.
They want to get married today, right?
Guys... we're not getting married.
Today we want to confess
something in church.
I think you should come with us.
What confession?
I think it's an old affair.
What are you saying?
- 100 percent, come on.
- Come.
God... we're going to be starting
a new life from tomorrow.
We're going to be getting married.
But this morning... something happened...
Sarah's special kids,
her, Jenny, me.
All 3 of us really got disturbed.
There's one boy, Simon.
He has a problem with his leg.
Some boys teased him.
They made fun of
him because of his leg.
Made fun of him.
The moment I asked them,
those boys started lying.
That we didn't imitate him.
I made them realize that
they were completely wrong.
They were not only mocking
Simon for being handicapped...
...but also lying.
And then... when Sarah told us,
what happened with her...
...we three realized that we've
been doing the same thing with papa.
We've been pretending too.
We've been lying to papa as well.
And that is why we're
all here to confess.
God, we really love each other...
...but we've committed a very big sin.
I don't know whether
You'll forgive us or not.
He will forgive you my children.
Because whatever you have done,
you've done it for one reason.
And that is love. Real love.
So He will forgive you.
It would've been wrong
if you had done these things...
...for greed.
For money.
Or for other worldly desires.
But you did it for true love.
God will bless you my children.
"My mind's here,
but my heart's somewhere else."
"Everything is fair,
in love and war."
"Papa."
"Papa.".
"My emotions are shaken up."
"Like a banana's been peeled."
"Love has shaken up up."
"Papa.".
"It was so fake..."
"My love... my love."
"Now it seems divine."
"It was so fake..."
"My love... my love."
"Now it seems divine."
Hey, pass the ball.
What's wrong with you'?
- Sorry! Sorry! Sorry! Sorry!
"Love is such a scoundrel."
"Makes you sweat."
"Makes your life difficult."
"From heaven I've been
pushed to hell." - Open. Open.
"From heaven I've
been pushed to hell."
"we played the game of love."
Open up, hurry up in there.
I can't control it.
"Papa.".
"It was so fake..."
"My love... my love."
"Now it seems divine."
"Papa.".
"It was so fake..."
"My love... my love."
"Now it seems divine."
"Papa.".
Let's go and tell
the girls the truth.
That till date
we did everything for money.
And that we actually love them.
Come on.
Jenny just messaged me.
She called us at the wax factory.
Jenny lovingly made some
wax statue for me.
And the three girls are coming there.
So let's go there.
We'll tell them everything clearly.
Come on.
Oh God, what a place.
Rock!
Jackie Chan.
- Your Ronaldo.
- Yeah.
Teddy.
Your statue looks so real.
Who's that with his legs in the air?
That's Tiger Shroff.
What nonsense do you keep saying?
Must admit you three
played really well...
By pretending to be blind,
mute and crippled.
Rajeev, the real fun begins now...
...when we beat these
normal guys to death.
Hey...
He can single-handedly
deal with all of you.
Ladies and Gentlemen, to my right...
...weighing 188 pounds.
And to my left, standing 6 feet tall.
The brawler,
the kicker... the footballer...
The junkyard's junk.
I mean the player of all players.
Sorry...
And he's going to...
One... two...
"Your mother-sister...
Mother-sister... Mother-sister..."
All you guys will get beat up.
Sandy will slap you all so hard.
With backward legs,
you all will reach Khandala's hills.
"Your mother-sister...
Mother-sister... Mother-sister..."
Let's sit.
Do you have some snacks?
Popcorn.
What's wrong with this Indian?
...Indian!"
No!
No, no, no, he said Indica.
- He said Indiana Jones.
He said Indonesia.
- He said Indigo.
Guys... guys... I am okay.
Thank God,
but he didn't say Indian.
You dog!
Now you two will get beaten up.
No, I won't let my friends die.
Sandy...
I am gonna let you two die.
Save us.
He's hurting himself.
Keep saying Indian..
Save me.
Sundi, stop.
Sundi is going to knock you out.
Sundi will ring your bell.
Save me.
No Sundi, for my sake.
You dog.
"Let me go home...
One minute.
- what are you doing?
"Let me go home...
Now you're dead, Sandy.
Michael.
I am saved. I am saved. I saved.
No! - "I beloved,
can't live without you."
Are you okay?
Come. - "I beloved,
can'! Live without you."
Now this has become personal.
What's this message?
Those three are normal?
Are you mad?
Who is it?
Boys... boys... it's me, your daddy.
Let's get out of here...
...and go tell Urja Nagre that
these three are not handicapped.
Wow... wax statues of
you dues as well. Superb.
You made Urja Nagre
your sons' dad only for wealth.
Now we'll go tell Urja.
And Urja Nagre will
come here and take your pee!
I mean... he will settle his score.
Hold on... if you squeal on us,
we're dead.
But if we expose you,
you three are dead too.
So the deal is... you guys
can marry Urja Nagre's daughters...
...but we want equal
shares in his wealth.
Batook Patel,
I want every penny accounted for.
Here's the calculator.
So... the wealth's worth 50 billion.
Divided into 7 skates.
That comes to...
Around 7 billion each.
- Divide by 8.
- Why 8?
- There's two of me.
- Huh!
Sundi and Sandy.
What nonsense...
- Should I call Urja?
Divide by 8.
So that's...
50 divide by 8...
6 billion per head.
One minute.
I'm a chef for the world,
but actually...
...I am an undercover FBI agent.
I'm joking!
"Pasta."
I received a message
that you're all here.
Now I want equal share in the money.
50 billion divide by 9.
That means...
5 billion each.
Hey, one minute.
10, 11, 12...
Divide by 12.
4 billion each.
Hey... don't divide by 12,
divide by 15.
Why?
We have your sons" babies in our womb.
Yeah.
Womb?
Idiot.
- Rascals, you learned to ride a bike,
but not to wear a helmet.
Batook, congratulations.
You've become a grandfather.
Whatever! 13, 14, 15.
3 billion each!
Great.
I worked so hand for 15 years,
only to get 3 billion...
Sorry, Mr. Rajnikant.
Did you hear?
Do you want a share too?
Speak up.
Oh... Mr. Obama. You heard it too.
Do you want a share as well?
And what are you looking at?
You got your share!
Urja. Your statue.
What are you looking at?
We're splitting you money only.
You always keep saying BJK... ATM... etc...
I saw Saraswati's picture
on Bunty's laptop.
And while watching it...
"Listen what say Mr. Bachchan."
"speak... speak... speak."
I called Batook to tell
the truth about you three.
It was out of reach,
so I called on the office landline.
'But your orphan plan was a flop.'
'I am your father, get it.'
'I got Urja Nagre arrested. You guys
have no idea what all I have done.'
Every dog is loyal.
But my own trustworthy
chap turned out to be a dog.
I messaged all of
you using a software.
Because I want to give.
SMS.
Death Sentence to everyone.
Mamma-Mia.
Who wants to die first?
- Me! I want to die first.
I am leaving.
Urja, don't shoot me to pieces.
Kill them.
- No, no... him.
- Beat them.
No! Shoot them!
- Shoot these buggers.
No!
Urja...
My first name means last so,
I'll be at the end of the line.
It was the question of all babies,
forgive us.
Urja Nagre, if you kill us...
- Then our father will be an orphan!
Kill our dad.
Urja Nagre... the door of
your heart should always be big...
...because even computers have windows.
Delhi Agra...
Skirt blouse...
Dhokla Khakra.
Hunku Pakhre.
It's Urja Nagre!
Then you only talk.
You see, sir...
...wherever I stand,
the line ends there only.
Hey!
Okay bye!
Nagre sir, don't shoot me.
If you shoot me,
you'll be sentenced to life.
And you'll also be hanged.
Because there's two of me. Two.
- Sandy, Sundi... two.
- Shut up!
Now all of you will DIE.
Full form.
No full form. All will die.
"Pasta."
where is everyone hiding?
This way... this way.
Lookalike! Lookalike! Lookalike!
No!
Where's Urja?
- Urja!
- Why you!
Ronaldo's clothes?
Mummy!
What are you doing?
It's me your brother.
Look, look, look.
Look, look... wire, wire.
Urja.
Hey! Hey!
Sandy!
Slow. .Slow.
What happened?
We didn't get the
wealth because of you.
And... now you won't get
the girls love because of us.
Got it.
You dog!
Shoved it in, but don't twist it.
- Don't twist it!
- Sandy.
What did you guys do?
- why did you guys do this for us?
Sandy.
That day in the church...
you three confessed in front of God.
Today we want to confess too.
- what?
Actually, all three of
us suffer from split personalities.
First it was for money,
but now it's for love.
Correct.
- Teddy.
- Yes.
Oh, Bunty.
- I love you.
- What?
I mean sister-in-law... sister-in-law...
Slow...
Sister-in-law.
Everyone go to their girl.
Saraswati.
Saraswati. Saraswati. Saraswati.
I love you, my darling.
I love you.
- I love you.
And listen, forgive this man too.
Because Batook isn't your father,
Urja Nagre is.
Yes.
- What?
- Yes.
He's your father.
Go.
- Papa.
Don't worry, daddy.
You served time for your crimes right?
Yes.
Papa... whatever
you were for the world...
...but for us,
you will always be our father.
Yes.
And we're all proud of you.
We're so proud of you, daddy.
Me too. Love you my babies.
- we're finally together.
Hey... - Sorry..
Don't do it.
Sandy.
- Bunty.
- Give me the gun.
All done... finally done.
All's well that ends well.
- Yes.
And papa,
we want to have an Indian wedding.
"Indian."
"Bloody love..."
"Bloody love... From today
love will be like a prayer."
"Bloody love..."
That's enough.
"Bloody love... From today
love will be like a prayer."
Bunty, stop leaning on me.
Wo... shoot, murder...
I forgot.
Where are you going?
- Help me, help me.
- Wait, wait.
A goon came with a knife... shh... shh...
I did...
"You look so sexy."
"Your gorgeous body..."
"Your gorgeous body, blows my mind."
"Your hot figure, blows my mind."
" Anyone you trap,
only God can save him."
"I've never seen anyone
like you." - Let go of the button.
"Expensive liners,
and those dangly earrings."
"The glittering skirt..."
"...and the way you sway
that waist is priceless."
Hey! I'm dead. - "Expensive liners,
and those dangly earrings."
"The glittering skirt..."
"...and the way you sway
that waist is priceless."
That day I...
- Sir... sir...
- what?
Wait... it's my dialogue.
Sir, the camera isn't rolling.
And yes...
The cameraman went on a lunch-break.
"You're the richest girl
in the world, sweetheart."
Come on, son.
This looks bad at this age.
You want to marry Batook?
Crap!
Where did you go?
Slap me again quickly.
You...
You always leave before.
Okay, sorry it's my mistake.
Why you... perfect.
My pants are very tight.
Akshay, get out soon...
or I won't give you your cheque.
'Rock-a-by baby...'
Milk...
Milk bowls.
Who am I now?
Sandy.
I forgot.
Who am I now?
"Bloody love..."
"Bloody love... From today
love will be like a prayer."
"You're the richest, darling."
"Housefull three."
"If you become my dear, like
a small baby I'll take care of you."
"when we're in love, then
why did your father call the priest?"
"I've just one thing to say to you,
I sweat..."
"...you're stuck to
me like chewing gum."
"Oh baby, have mercy on our love."
"You're my bread, and I am you jam."
"Life is short,
let's say those sweet-nothings."
"If you say it once,
I'll do anything for you."
"This is your chance,
and also the ritual..."
"...but why you standing far."
"Take me in your arms,
like a true prince."
"The moons showing attitude."
"Even the sun's talking gibberish."
"In this awesome weather
give me a English kiss."
"You're the richest girl in the world,
sweetheart."
"Bloody love..."
"Bloody love... From today
love will be like a prayer."
"You're the richest, darling."
"Housefull three."
"Bloody love..."
"You're the richest girl in the world,
sweetheart."
"Bloody love..."
"You're the richest, darling."
"You're the richest girl in the world,
sweetheart."
"Bloody love..."
"You're the richest, darling."